<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<factions>
  <humans>
    <friendly>
      <flavor>Lots of life and joyeous sounds emminates from the distance. The humans living here sure seem nice.</flavor>
      <flavor>When approaching, a warm welcome is being shown towards you by the humans living there.</flavor>
    </friendly>
    <neutral>
      <flavor>As you approach, the people living there go inside. I don't think they care much about your presence.</flavor>
      <flavor>All the people just stand back and look at you as you approach. they seem confused.</flavor>
    </neutral>
    <enemy>
      <flavor>The people here are aggressive towards you. they do not like intruders.</flavor>
      <flavor>The people living nearby do not want to be disturbed, and you just have. They are not happy about that.</flavor>
    </enemy>
  </humans>

  <highbourne>
    <friendly>
      <flavor>A small group of highbournes are gathered up and are waving happily as you approach their settlement.</flavor>
      <flavor>Your presence is accepted with smiling faces from the locals, as you approach.</flavor>
    </friendly>
    <neutral>
      <flavor>The people here don't look friendly, but they don't look dangerous either.</flavor>
      <flavor>The highbournes seem to be slightly confused as to what you want.</flavor>
    </neutral>
    <enemy>
      <flavor>You have entered the realm of the highbournes. they are not pleased by this intrusion.</flavor>
      <flavor>These creatures, the highbournes, are not looking very inviting. They don't say much, but you feel eery.</flavor>
    </enemy>
  </highbourne>

  <nomads>
    <friendly>
      <flavor>The Nomads seem pleased by your visit and are gathering to see who you are.</flavor>
      <flavor>The nomadic children wants to play with you. They sure are a curious bunch!</flavor>
    </friendly>
    <neutral>
      <flavor>Eyes stare blankly at you. The nomads seem startled by your presence.</flavor>
      <flavor>As you approach, the nomadic people living here seem indifferent to your existence.</flavor>
    </neutral>
    <enemy>
      <flavor>The nomads here may be peaceful normally, but they seem to be aggravated by you as you are approaching.</flavor>
      <flavor>The Nomads do not like to share, as that will reduce their resources. They are willing to fight if needed.</flavor>
    </enemy>
  </nomads>
</factions>