<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<specialEvents>
  <combination type="HumansMINE">
    <type>HumanMine</type>
    <intro>While you were in the mines of </intro>
    <body>
      your machinery left behind a lot of oil staines on the floor, and the Humans living on that island were quickly aware that you had been there.
    </body>
    <extra>
      They want to know how your machinery works, and how they can use it to drive
      away the Nomads.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Invite them into your castle to show them how it works.
        </button>
        <ally>
          The humans take notes on how to build the precious machinery.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They are happy to learn your methods and have a peace offering.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          The humans were not really expecting your cooperation, and
          agrees to spare your crew.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>Tell them that you don't support wars, and that you can't tell them.</button>
        <ally>
          They understand your views, and one of the humans offer
          a crystal piece in hopes that you will change your mind.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They seem mildly dissappointed, but one of them agrees with you
          and offers himself to join your cause.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They weren't expecting you to cooperate, so they use brute force and
          take out one of your crew.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
  <combination type="HumansFACTORY">
    <type>HumanFactory</type>
    <intro>
      Your machinery left behind large tracks all over the floor in the factory of 
    </intro>
    <body>
      . And the humans that used to run that factory have taken notice of your visit.
    </body>
    <extra>
      They want to learn about your machines and get the blueprints so they can make
      their own machinery and take the land of the Highbournes.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Give them the blueprints and a tutorial on how to make them.
        </button>
        <ally>
          They appreciate your help and give you a gift in return for your help.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          The humans cheer. They were getting desperate.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They are stunned that you would actually share this information with them.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>Tell them to make their own machines and back off your intellectual property.</button>
        <ally>
          They are mildly insulted, but understands your point.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          The humans were not really expecting you to help out, but they leave
          you a peace offering.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They expected you to decline, and were prepared for this outcome.
          They start hacking on your castle.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
  <combination type="HighbournesFOREST">
    <type>HighbourneForest</type>
    <intro>
      Down in the vast forests of 
    </intro>
    <body>
      , your cleric set up protective wards all over the place, and the Highbournes
      living there have walked straight into them and are aware of your visit.
    </body>
    <extra>
      They want you to tell them how to remove it, as it can cause Nomads to
      come wandering in.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Give them the counter measures for the wards.
        </button>
        <ally>
          You have redeemed your previous mistake,
          and they bow their heads at you.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They thank you for your cooperation and put forward an herb you have
          never seen before.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They turn around, arrogantly, and walks away.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>Tell them that you can not remove them, and that they are forever.</button>
        <ally>
          They are upset at this and decide to cast a spell of sickness on one of your crew.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They seem displeased, but they accept the reality anyways.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          The Highbourne leader looks at one of your crew with fiery eyes, and
          the crew falls down lifeless.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
  <combination type="HighbournesMAGICSITE">
    <type>HighbourneMagic</type>
    <intro>
      Your cleric made a holy chant when you were at the magic site of 
    </intro>
    <body>
      , and some Highbournes heard it and have followed you ever since. 
    </body>
    <extra>
      They feel that your holy chanting was blasphemous to their beliefs and they
      want you to apologize, like the humans never did.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Apologize politely and say that it will never happen again.
        </button>
        <ally>
          They know you by reputation and they forgive you...this time.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          Highbournes need more than excuses. You did not manage to
          convince them.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They leave without a word. You have no idea what they are thinking.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>Refuse to apologize and explain that you have the right to your own beliefs.</button>
        <ally>
          The highbournes respect your right to believe in what you want.
          But they want to send one of them to follow you and observe the righteousness
          of your actions.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They seem impressed by your rightful mind. You might have ganed
          their respect.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          "Your castle starts crumbling as their chief raises his arms.
          He is using his magical powers to punish you.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
  <combination type="NomadsWRECKAGE">
    <type>NomadWreckage</type>
    <intro>
      During the exploration of the wreckage on 
    </intro>
    <body>
      , the nomads have seen your alchemist preparing some potions.
    </body>
    <extra>
       Their people has recently suffered a disease caused by the Highbournes, and
      alchemic knowledge might prove useful to them.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Teach them how to create basic potions to help them face epidemics efficiently
        </button>
        <ally>
          You have helped them more than you can imagine today. They decide
          to repay you with what little they have.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They are pleased by your choice, and they will remember it.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          Your reaction is unexpected. They will remember the help you gave
          them today.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>
          Apologize and explain that you need the alchemy potions to yourself in case
          your crew gets diseases of their own.
        </button>
        <ally>
          Your decline is making them very upset. You decide to leave as the
          situation is becoming dangerous.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They understand your choice but seem disapointed
          as you leave them to their doom.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          Your reputation preceded you and they your decline was expected.
          They seem to be ready for anything to get what they want.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
  <combination type="NomadsVILLAGE">
    <type>NomadVillage</type>
    <intro>
      After you left the village on the island of 
    </intro>
    <body>
      the nomads have seen you making use of your alchemic powers. 
    </body>
    <extra>
      The village you visited has recently been salvaged by a local group of human bandits.
      The nomads are asking for revenge and your alchemic skills have impressed them.
    </extra>
    <options>
      <one>
        <button>
          Show them how to make your impressive potions and send them on their way.
        </button>
        <ally>
          They observe you and leave to prepare their revenge.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          They observe you and leave to prepare their revenge.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          Pain has driven them mad, they  attack you to salvage your castle.
          Your crew fights them back and you quickly leave.
        </enemy>
      </one>
      <two>
        <button>
          Explain to them that revenge is probably not the solution and decline their
          demand.
        </button>
        <ally>
          They are impressed by your peaceful methods. One of   them
          would like to join your crew.
        </ally>
        <neutral>
          Peaceful thoughts will not ease their craving for revenge.
          They will remember that.
        </neutral>
        <enemy>
          They are too tired to be upset. You hope that avoiding violence was
          the best way to help them.
        </enemy>
      </two>
    </options>
  </combination>
</specialEvents>